cherrybam.com 2009-04-13

# Privacy Policy

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with this web site. We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). 

We do not collect any information about our visitor's email or referring domain. For visitors on our website we collect Aggregate (General Tracking) information about pages that users visit on our site. 

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site. 

What Are Cookies?   
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function as effectively when viewed by the users. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses. 

With respect to cookies: We do not set any cookies. However, third parties may be placing and reading cookies on browsers, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on CherryBam.com. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on CherryBam.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to CherryBam.com and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some some features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. 

In the event that you might need to contact us, our email is [here](mailto:cherrybamlayouts@gmail.com).
